All right.
Baiklah.
Let's start by looking for
Mari kita mulai dengan melihat
the name key in the example JSON response from the Twitter API request.
kunci 'name' dalam contoh respon JSON dari permintaan API Twitter.
By searching the response for the name key,
Dengan menelusuri respons untuk kunci 'name',
we actually see that it appears multiple times for different uses.
kita melihat bahwa kunci 'name' itu muncul beberapa kali untuk penggunaan berbeda.
Sometimes the value is Tony Fadell.
Kadang nilainya adalah Tony Fadell.
Sometimes the value is Sebastian Thrun, and sometimes it's Udacity.
Kadang Sebastian Thrun, dan kadang Udacity.
In all three cases,
Di ketiga case ini,
the value appears to be a string that represents the name of a Twitter user.
nilai muncul sebagai string yang mewakili nama pengguna Twitter.
So in the quiz, the name key maps to the string JSON primitive.
Jadi dalam kuis, kunci 'name' merujuk pada string primitif JSON.
Next, we'll look for the user key.
Lalu, kita akan cari kunci 'user'.
The user key maps to a value that is enclosed in curly braces.
Kunci 'user' merujuk pada nilai yang berada dalam tanda kurung kurawal.
That means it maps to a JSON object with a lot more attributes about that Twitter
Artinya, ia merujuk pada objek JSON dengan lebih banyak atribut tentang pengguna
user with the name shernazdaver, screen_name, and other information.
Twitter itu yang bernama shernazdaver, screen_name, dan informasi lain.
If you look at the other cases where user appears,
Jika Anda lihat case-case lain di mana kunci 'user' muncul,
you'll find other Twitter users.
Anda akan menemukan pengguna Twitter lain.
So that means the user key maps to a JSON object.
Artinya, kunci 'user' merujuk pada objek JSON.
Next, we'll look for the hashtags key.
Lalu, kita mencari kunci 'hashtags'.
The hashtags key maps to a JSON array
Kunci 'hashtags' merujuk pada array JSON
because it points to a value with square brackets.
karena menunjuk suatu nilai dengan kurung persegi.
There's one hashtag in this tweet which is I\/O 16.
Ada satu 'hastag' dalam tweet ini yaitu I\/O 16.
This is the hashtag for the 2016 Google IO conference.
Ini adalah tagar untuk konferensi Google IO 2016.
If there are more hashtags in this tweet, they would show up in this array.
Jika ada lebih banyak 'hashtag' dalam tweet ini, akan muncul di array ini.
So the hashtag key maps to a JSON array.
Jadi kunci 'hashtags' merujuk pada array JSON.
Next, we'll look for the followers_count key.
Lalu, kita mencari kunci followers_count.
The key followers_count maps to the number of followers this
Kunci followers_count merujuk pada jumlah pengikut yang dimiliki
Twitter user has, which is 460291 in this case.
pengguna Twitter ini, yang dalam hal ini 460291.
So the followers count key maps to a JSON Primitive.
Jadi kunci followers_count merujuk pada JSON primitif.
Which is an integer in this case.
Yang dalam hal ini berupa bilangan bulat.